

Professional Summary

I'm a UX - UI Designer with 8 years of work experience in startups and tech companies. Currently working on the **UI-UX of an enterprise-level digital assistant platform** for the financial services industry.

Basil, K

UX-UI Product Designer

⋈ basilk212@gmail.com



+91 9895 441 576



Malappuram, Kerala



Portfolio website

Technical Skills

Figma Sketch Illustrator Photoshop HTML/CSS

Design skills

User Flow

Angular

Information Architecture

Wireframing

Interaction Design

User Interface Design

Mock-ups

Prototyping

Employment

UX - UI Product Designer

(Jan, 2016 - Present

6years

- Working on patent-pending DIY platform that enables enterprise users to launch intelligent Digital Assistants in weeks without writing a single line of code.
- Conceptualise designs that solve complex problems by creating user flows, wireframes, mocks and prototypes.
- Collaborate with multidisciplinary teams to communicate my design solutions with a high level of impact. Advocate for users' needs during product and design reviews.
- Deliver designs for each release by following up on implementation and fit and finish with engineering teams.
- Improve the look and feel of a wireframe into the hi-fidelity user interface.
- Contribute to improving, maintaining, and adopting the design system.
- Design Creatives for social media platforms, banners for marketing campaigns.

Web and Graphic Designer

(Jun, 2014 - Dec 2015

1.7 years

- Create wireframes or mockups for web pages and applications
- Design Creatives for social media platforms, banners for marketing campaigns
- · Incorporating functionalities and features into websites.
- Convert web design mockups to responsive html websites.

Education

Bachelor of Multimedia Communication

⑤ Sep, 2009 - Jun 2012

O University of Calicut

3 years